'use strict';
const STORE = [
  {
    question: "Why do cats rub themselves against their owners' legs and ankles?",
    
    answers: ["It's a sign of hunger", "It's a way of greeting", "It's a display of affection", "It's a type of scent marking"],
    
    correctAnswer: "It's a type of scent marking"
    
  },

  {
    question: 'Why do cats roll onto their back and show you their belly?',
    answers: ['They are being playful', 'They are feeling anxious', 'They want you to pet their belly', 'It\'s a sign of trust'],
    correctAnswer: 'It\'s a sign of trust'
    
  },

  {
    question: 'How high can most cats jump?',
    answers: ['About 3 feet','About 4 feet', 'About 5 feet', 'About 6 feet'],
    correctAnswer:'About 5 feet'
    
  },

  {
    question: 'Which of the following senses is the poorest developed in a cat?',
    answers: ['Smell', 'Hearing', 'Sight', 'They are all well developed'],
    correctAnswer: 'Sight'
    
  },

  {
    question: 'Giving your kitty catnip might cause it to:',
    answers: ['Be sleepy', 'Be energetic', 'Do nothing', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'All of the above'
   
  },

  {
    question: 'What is a cat doing when it’s “making biscuits?”',
    answers: ['Playing with bread dough', 'Kneading with its paws', 'Training to be a chef',  'Auditing for a Food Network show'],
    correctAnswer: 'Kneading with its paws'
    
  },

  {
    question: 'Calico cats are almost always:',
    answers: ['Left pawed', 'Female', 'Friendly', 'Finicky'],
    correctAnswer: 'Female'
    
  },

  {
    question: "What does it mean when a cat's fur is standing up and the back is arched?",
    answers: ['The cat is sad', 'The cat is playful', 'The cat is angry or scared', 'The cat wants to mate'],
    correctAnswer: 'The cat is angry or scared'
   
  },

  {
    question: "Cats perspire through their _______",
    answers: ['Whiskers', 'Ears', 'Hair', 'Paws'],
    correctAnswer: 'Paws'
  },

  {
    question: 'What can cats not taste?',
    answers: ['Sour', 'Sweet', 'Bitter', 'Salt'],
    correctAnswer: 'Sweet'
  },
]